parfois.com 2014-06-25

# Privacy Policy Parfois

Parfois is committed to protecting your privacy and developing technology that gives you the most powerful and safe online experience. This Statement of Privacy applies to the Parfois Web-site and governs data collection and usage. By using the Parfois website, you consent to the data practices described in this statement.

## Collection of your Personal Information

We collect information about you for 2 reasons:

1st -  to process your order  

2nd -  to provide you with the best service possible.

We will e-mail you to keep you up to date with your orders. We will also give you the opportunity to unsubscribe on all marketing emails.

Parfois will collect personally identifiable information, such as:

1 - Your e-mail address  

2 - Name  

3 - Addresses (home or work)   

4 - Telephone number.   

5 – Country and/or City  

6 – Date of Birth

> Please keep in mind that if you directly disclose personal information or personally sensitive data through Parfois public message boards, such as our [faceboo](http://www.facebook.com/parfois)k page, [tweeter](http://twitter.com/PARFOIS_) or [blog](http://parfoisaccessories.blogspot.com/), this information may be seen and used by others. 

Note: Parfois does not read any of your private online communications at your own webpages.

## Use of your Personal Information

Parfois collects and uses your personal information to operate the Parfois Web site and deliver the services you have requested. Parfois also uses your personal information to inform you of other products or services available at Parfois and its affiliates. Parfois may also contact you for surveys to conduct research about your opinion on current services or on potential new services that may be offered.

Parfois does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties. Parfois may, from time to time, contact you on behalf of external business partners about a particular offering that may be of interest to you. In those cases, your personal information (e-mail, name, address, telephone number) is not transferred to the third party. In addition, Parfois may share data with trusted partners to help us perform statistical analysis – (via email or postal mail) provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries/collections. All such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to Parfois and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information.

Parfois does not use or disclose sensitive personal information, without your explicit consent.

Parfois keeps track of the Web sites and pages our customers visit within Parfois.com, in order to determine what Parfois services are the most popular. This data is used to deliver customized content and advertising to customers whose behavior indicates that they are interested in a particular area of our website/product.

Parfois Web-sites will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to:

(a) Conform to the law-decrees or comply with legal process served on Parfois or the site;   

(b) Protect and defend the rights or property of Parfois;   

(c) Act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of     Parfois, or the public.

> ## Security of your Personal Information

Parfois secures the personal information you provide on computer servers in a controlled, secure environment, protected from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. When personal information (such as a credit card number) is transmitted to other Web sites, it is protected through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol signed by Digicert .

## Changes to this Statement

Parfois will occasionally update this Statement of Privacy to reflect company and customer feedback. Parfois encourages you to periodically review this Statement to be informed of how Parfois is protecting your information.

## Contact Information

Parfois welcomes your comments regarding this Statement of Privacy. If you believe that Parfois has not adhered to this Statement, please contact us. We will take into consideration your suggestions to promptly determine and try to solve the problem.
